PETER JANASZ

3009 E Emile Zola Ave Phoenix, AZ 85032 602-689-0051

petertjanasz@gmail.com

Highly motivated medical professional with 18 years' experience in the operating room setting. Ability to work in a team setting while exhibiting mutual respect, dedication, integrity, and excellence. Able to take ownership to work independently to fulfill responsibilities at a high standard.

EXPERIENCE

ANESTHESIA TECH SUPERVISOR, MAYO CLINIC OF ARIZONA

SEPTEMBER 2021-PRESENT

Responsible for 20 anesthesia support staff members, including anesthesia techs and anesthesia PCAs. Responsible for onboarding new staff and maintaining competencies with existing staff. Implements new policy and standards to abide by JCAHO regulations. Collaborates with CRNA and leadership consultants to provide a high standard in patient care and implement new workflow changes to accomplish these standards. Establishes and maintains positive relationships with staff across multiple departments involved with anesthesia patients. On-call duties which include heart, liver and kidney transplant procedures.

ANETHESIA TECH TEAM LEAD, MAYO CLINIC OF ARIZONA

AUGUST 2019 – SEPTEMBER 2021

Responsible for precepting new staff during their orientation process, including participation in "buddy call" with new staff to familiarize them with on-call responsibilities. Collaborates with ICU department to provide support during the COVID pandemic, together with the training of anesthesia techs to provide support to ICU nurses and respiratory techs that care for COVID patients. Training others in skills such as arterial line placement, opening central line kits using sterile technique, and proper use of PPE. On-call duties which include heart, liver and kidney transplant procedures.

ANETHESIA TECH, MAYO CLINIC OF ARIZONA

MAY 2007 - AUGUST 2019

On-call duties which include heart, liver, and kidney transplant procedures. Proficiency in invasive procedures such as arterial line placement. Assist anesthesia providers by maintaining and managing anesthesia supplies and equipment. Assistance in sterile procedures such as nerve blocks, central line placement, difficult intubations, and mass transfusion protocols. Responsible for running cell savage during high blood loss surgical procedures. Troubleshooting Drager anesthesia machines and other essential anesthesia equipment.

ANETHESIA PATIENT CARE ASSISTANT, MAYO CLINIC OF ARIZONA

OCTOBER 2005 - MAY 2007

Assist anesthesia providers by stocking and maintaining anesthesia supplies and equipment.

SKILLS

- Surgical aseptic technique and maintenance of the sterile field
- Excellent written/verbal communication skills
- Troubleshooting of medical equipment and supplies
- Critical thinking and problem solving
- Prioritization of multiple tasks during stressful situations.
- Proficient in Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint, and Outlook

EDUCATION

MAY 2003

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA, DESERT MOUNTAIN HIGH SCHOOL

SOME COLLEGE, MARICOPA COMMUNITY COLLEGES

Prerequisites for Nursing, Health Science

CERTIFICATES

OCTOBER 2022
BASIC LIFE SUPPORT CERTIFICATE

REFERALS

Available upon request